export const dummyData = {
	"Japanese Adverbs": {
		title: "Japanese Adverbs",
		questions: [
			{
				question: "ゆっくり",
				answer: "slowly"
			},
			{
				question: "のんびり",
				answer: "quietly, freely, leisurely"
			},
			{
				question: "いっしょうけんめい",
				answer: "very hard"
			},
			{
				question: "じょじょに",
				answer: "gradually, little by little"
			}
		]
	},
	"Japanese Verbs": {
		title: "Japanese Verbs",
		questions: [
			{
				question: "せいちょうする",
				answer: "to mature, grow as a person"
			},
			{
				question: "しげきする",
				answer: "to inspire, stimulate"
			},
			{
				question: "かむ",
				answer: "to bite, chew"
			},
			{
				question: "しょうたいする",
				answer: "to invite"
			}
		]
	},
	"Tokyo Station Names": {
		title: "Tokyo Station Names",
		questions: [
			{
				question: "四谷",
				answer: "Yotsuya"
			},
			{
				question: "荻窪",
				answer: "Ogikubo"
			},
			{
				question: "品川",
				answer: "Shinagawa"
			},
			{
				question: "明大前",
				answer: "Meidaimae"
			}
		]
	}
};
